A Guide to the Governor Mark R. Warner, Press Office records, 2001-2006 (bulk 2002-2006)
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Photographs, 2001-2005 (Accession 42460).
  - Subseries B. Event files, 2001-2005 (Accession 42460).
    - Agency head meeting and IT Reform bill signing, 2003 May 5 (Box 68, Folder 67)
    - Agency head reception, 2003 May 5 (Box 68, Folder 68)
    - Governor's salute to law enforcement candlelight ceremony, 2003 May 5 (Box 68, Folder 68)
    - Greater Richmond Pipes and Drums photos, 2003 May 5 (Box 68, Folder 68)
    - Bill Mezger of VEC retirement photo op, 2003 May 6 (Box 68, Folder 69)
    - Heroes in Healthcare reception, 2003 May 6 (Box 68, Folder 70)
    - Virginia Public Service Week, Governor's Awared ceremony, 2003 May 7 (Box 68, Folder 71)
    - WCDX interview about PASS program, 2003 May 8 (Box 68, Folder 72)
    - PASS school visits, Carver, Chimborazo and Maymont Elementary schools, 2003 May 8 (Box 68, Folder 72)
    - Bill signings, HB 1820, HB 1675, SB 695, SB 1138, HB 2128, HB 2525, HB 2486, SB 952, SB 1151, HB 2447, SB 152, and HB 1727, 2003 May 9 (Box 68, Folder 73)
    - "Levey Live" on WashingtonPost.com webcast, 2003 May 27 (Box 68, Folder 74)
    - PASS school visit, Blackwell Elementary, 2003 May 28 (Box 68, Folder 75)
    - K-12 Initiative, 2003 June 3 (Box 68, Folder 76)
    - Genesis Preparatory Academy Capitol visit, 2003 June 3 (Box 68, Folder 77)
    - Sale of General Obligation Bonds media event, 2003 June 4 (Box 68, Folder 78)
    - Virginia Baton Twirling Champions photo op, 2003 June 5 (Box 68, Folder 79)
    - Central Virginia Foodbanks' National Hunger Awareness Day event, 2003 June 5 (Box 68, Folder 80)
    - Standing Vice Minister of Foreign Affairs of Vietnam courtesy visit, 2003 June 5 (Box 68, Folder 81)
    - BRAC meeting, 2003 June 6 (Box 68, Folder 82)
    - Naval base tour, 2003 June 6 (Box 68, Folder 82)
    - DGS/Biotech building dedication, 2003 June 6 (Box 68, Folder 82)
    - Governor visits Parksley, VA, 2003 June 7 (Box 68, Folder 83)
    - Virginia 2007 Community Program announcement, 2003 June 11 (Box 68, Folder 84)
    - Tour and employee meeting at Infineon Technologies, 2003 June 11 (Box 68, Folder 85)
    - Bill signings, HB 2097, HB 1929, HB 1930, SB 1194, SB 1121 and SB 956, 2003 June 12 (Box 68, Folder 86)
    - Girls State and Boys State, 2003 June 18 (Box 68, Folder 87)
    - NBA event, 2003 June 18 (Box 68, Folder 87)
    - Bill signing, Hunters for the Hungry, 2003 June 18 (Box 68, Folder 87)
    - Literacy Foundation press conference, 2003 June 23 (Box 68, Folder 88)
    - Bill signings, HB 1764, SB 1102, and HB 2267, 2003 June 25 (Box 68, Folder 89)
    - The Jason Foundation meeting with Fran Rooker, 2003 June 25 (Box 68, Folder 89)
    - Wolfin' Down Books summer reading announcement, 2003 June 26 (Box 68, Folder 90)
    - Ask Why event, 2003 June 30 (Box 68, Folder 91)
    - Bayview celebration and ribbon cutting, 2003 July 2 (Box 68, Folder 92)
    - VITA birthday picnic, 2003 July 8 (Box 68, Folder 93)
    - Rock climbing at Little Stony Man Mountain, 2003 July 9 (Box 68, Folder 94)
    - Tax reform public meeting, 2003 July 10 (Box 68, Folder 95)
    - Virginia Citizenship Institute Capitol visit, 2003 July 10 (Box 68, Folder 96)
    - Governor's Regional Summer Academy, Brunswick County, 2003 July 11 (Box 68, Folder 97)
    - Governor's Fellows reception, roll A, 2003 July 22 (Box 68, Folder 98)
    - Governor's Fellows reception, roll B, 2003 July 22 (Box 68, Folder 99)
    - Roll-out of Spend Management Initiatives, Sandston, VA, 2003 July 23 (Box 68, Folder 100)
    - Roll-out of Spend Management Initiatives, Roanoke, VA, 2003 July 24 (Box 68, Folder 101)
    - Mission of Mercy volunteer event, 2003 July 24 (Box 68, Folder 101)
    - ARC grants announcement, 2003 July 25 (Box 68, Folder 102)
    - Automotive job announcement, 2003 July 30 (Box 68, Folder 103)
    - VEC stop-by, 2003 July 31 (Box 68, Folder 104)
    - Base Commanders meeting, 2003 Aug. 12 (Box 68, Folder 105)
    - Motor sports announcement, 2003 Aug. 13 (Box 68, Folder 106)
    - Biased-based policing announcement, 2003 Aug. 20 (Box 68, Folder 107)
    - Lunch with the Lottery, 2003 Aug. 20 (Box 68, Folder 108)
    - LifeNet/Virginia Organ Donor Registry event, 2003 Aug. 21 (Box 68, Folder 109)
    - Tom Bradshaw and Thomas Sears going away party stop-by, 2003 Aug. 21 (Box 68, Folder 110)
    - Dog photo ops, Buster and Beau at Governor's Mansion, 2003 Aug. 22 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - General Assembly Budget Committee meeting, 2003 Aug. 25 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - D.U.I./Checkpoint Strikeforce press conference, 2003 Aug. 25 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Virginia State Police trooper graduation, 2003 Aug. 29 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - eVA announcement, 2003 Sept. 2 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Education for a Lifetime kick-off, Richmond, 2003 Sept. 3 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Education for a Lifetime event, Danville, 2003 Sept. 5 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Suffolk Cemetery groundbreaking, 2003 Sept. 8 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Smart Smiles announcement, 2003 Sept. 8 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - School Audits Initiative announcement, 2003 Sept. 9 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Speech at Tucker High School, 2003 Sept. 11 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Board of Education meeting, 2003 Sept. 17 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Tidewater local elected officials conference call, 2003 Sept. 17 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - EOC press conference, 2003 Sept. 17 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Hurricane Isabel press announcement, 2003 Sept. 18 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Photos at Arthur Ashe Center shelter, 2003 Sept. 18 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Media tour with President Bush, 2003 Sept. 22 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Richmond hurricane damage press conference, 2003 Sept. 22 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Delivering meals at Red Cross, 2003 Sept. 23 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Tours of Claremont, Sunken Meadows and Smithfield Center, 2003 Sept. 24 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - High speed rail meeting, 2003 Sept. 29 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Senior Year Initiative, 2003 Oct. 1 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Virginia State Fair Kids Commonwealth Banner, Lisa Collis website, 2003 Oct. 3 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Forbes CEO Summit reception, 2003 Oct. 3 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Workforce Development System conference and education roll-out, 2003 Oct. 7 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Meeting with Israeli Ambassador, 2003 Oct. 7 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Latino Advisory Commission announcement, 2003 Oct. 7 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Teacher Retention Initiative, 2003 Oct. 8 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - 1st BRAC meeting, 2003 Oct. 10 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Higher Education Initiative announcement, 2003 Oct. 14 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Pre-K Initiative, 2003 Oct. 20 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Ronnie Wilson of DGS retirement party stop-by, 2003 Oct. 31 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Chip Canady of Capitol Police, 2003 Oct. 31 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - World Access U.S. Headquarters, 2003 Nov. 6 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Proclamation signing, Employee Support for the Guard and Reserve, 2003 Nov. 14 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Black Caucus lunch at Governor's Mansion, 2003 Nov. 14 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - CovaNet announcement and press event, 2003 Nov. 19 (Box 69, Folder 34)
    - College Boards reception, 2003 Nov. 19 (Box 69, Folder 35)
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation land conservation celebration, 2003 Nov. 20 (Box 69, Folder 35)
    - Virginia Corporation conference, 2003 Nov. 20 (Box 69, Folder 36)
    - Press announcement, tax reform, 2003 Nov. 24 (Box 69, Folder 37)
    - Tax reform announcements in Roanoke, Falls Church and Virginia Beach, 2003 Nov. 25 (Box 69, Folder 38)
    - American Indian tribute ceremony, 2003 Nov. 26 (Box 69, Folder 39)
    - Courtesy meeting with Rotem Company, 2003 Dec. 3 (Box 69, Folder 40)
    - Christmas decorations at the Governor's Mansion, 2003 Dec. 4 (Box 69, Folder 41)
    - Lighting of the state tree, 2003 Dec. 5 (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - Grand Illumination at James Center, 2003 Dec. 5 (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - Press reception, roll 1, 2003 Dec. 9 (Box 69, Folder 43)
    - Press reception, roll 2, 2003 Dec. 9 (Box 69, Folder 44)
    - Press reception, roll 3, 2003 Dec. 9 (Box 69, Folder 45)
    - VEDP reception, new/expanding CEOs, 2003 Dec. 10 (Box 69, Folder 46)
    - Crime in Minority Communities town hall meeting, 2003 Dec. 10 (Box 69, Folder 47)
    - Tax reform event, Newport News, 2003 Dec. 11 (Box 69, Folder 48)
    - Democrats' holiday reception, 2003 Dec. 12 (Box 69, Folder 49)
    - Tax calculator press conference, 2003 Dec. 15 (Box 69, Folder 50)
    - Joint General Assembly Money Committee meeting, 2003 Dec. 17 (Box 69, Folder 51)
    - Department of Labor and Industry photo op, 2003 Dec. 17 (Box 69, Folder 52)
    - Staff reception, 2003 Dec. 22 (Box 69, Folder 53)
    - Cookie decorating party at Hilliard House, 2003 Dec. 23 (Box 69, Folder 54)
    - Cookie decorating part at Hilliard House, 2003 Dec. 23 (Box 69, Folder 55)
    - Tour and luncheon in Poquoson, 2003 Dec. 23 (Box 69, Folder 55)
    - National Governors Association, Indianapolis, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 56)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, 2003 (1 of 4) (Box 69, Folder 57)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, 2003 (2 of 4) (Box 69, Folder 58)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, 2003 (3 of 4) (Box 69, Folder 59)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, 2003 (4 of 4) (Box 69, Folder 60)
    - Tax reform event, Hopewell/Prince George Chamber of Commerce, 2004 Jan. 9 (Box 69, Folder 61)
    - Meeting with Senator John Warner, 2004 Jan. 13 (Box 69, Folder 62)
    - Democratic Caucus reception, 2004 Jan. 13 (Box 69, Folder 63)
    - Senior citizen group stop-by, 2004 Jan. 14 (Box 69, Folder 64)
    - State of the Commonwealth speech, 2004 Jan. 14 (Box 69, Folder 65)
    - VEDP announcement in Martinsville, 2004 Jan. 15 (Box 69, Folder 66)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council annual banquet, 2004 Jan. 15 (Box 69, Folder 67)
    - Unity Day celebration, 2004 Jan. 18 (Box 69, Folder 68)
    - Rev. Charles Wormley photo op, 2004 Jan. 19 (Box 69, Folder 69)
    - Virginia Young Democrats photo op, 2004 Jan. 19 (Box 69, Folder 69)
    - Community Learning Week mass meeting, 2004 Jan. 19 (Box 69, Folder 70)
    - Buchanan County Board of Supervisors courtesy visit, 2004 Jan. 20 (Box 69, Folder 71)
    - American Legion, Department of Virginia courtesy visit, 2004 Jan. 20 (Box 69, Folder 71)
    - SCHEV Outstanding Faculty Awards ceremony, 2004 Jan. 21 (Box 69, Folder 72)
    - Dickenson County officials, 2004 Jan. 21 (Box 69, Folder 73)
    - Joint Engineers Council photo op, 2004 Jan. 22 (Box 69, Folder 74)
    - Radford University Advocacy Day photo op, 2004 Jan. 22 (Box 69, Folder 74)
    - New legislators' reception, 2004 Jan. 22 (Box 69, Folder 75)
    - Kids Commonwealth winner pizza delivery, 2004 Jan. 30 (Box 69, Folder 76)
    - Chesapeake and Virginia Beach students Capitol visit, 2004 Feb. 3 (Box 69, Folder 77)
    - Virginia Association of Elementary School Principals photo op, 2004 Feb. 3 (Box 69, Folder 77)
    - Virginia Tech alumni photo op, 2004 Feb. 4 (Box 69, Folder 78)
    - Men of Tomorrow photo op, 2004 Feb. 4 (Box 69, Folder 78)
    - Clinch Independent Living Agency photo op, 2004 Feb. 4 (Box 69, Folder 78)
    - House of Delegates legislative reception, 2004 Feb. 4 (Box 69, Folder 79)
    - Old Dominion Highway Contractors meeting, 2004 Feb. 4 (Box 69, Folder 80)
    - Old Dominion University Alumni Association photo op, 2004 Feb. 5 (Box 69, Folder 80)
    - Coffee reception for Sheriff's Association, 2004 Feb. 5 (Box 69, Folder 81)
    - Natural resources press conference, 2004 Feb. 6 (Box 69, Folder 82)
    - Miss Virginia, Nancy A. Redd photo op, 2004 Feb. 6 (Box 69, Folder 83)
    - VEA Foundation rally, 2004 Feb. 9 (Box 69, Folder 84)
    - Legislative Enhancement Advancement Program photo op, 2004 Feb. 9 (Box 69, Folder 85)
    - Surry County High School photo op, 2004 Feb. 10 (Box 69, Folder 86)
    - Russian legislators courtesy visit, 2004 Feb. 10 (Box 69, Folder 86)
    - Vice President of Democratic Republic of Congo visit, 2004 Feb. 10 (Box 69, Folder 87)
    - Battelle Memorial Institute photo op, 2004 Feb. 11 (Box 69, Folder 88)
    - Model General Assembly photo op, 2004 Feb. 11 (Box 69, Folder 88)
    - Budget impasse press conference, 2004 Mar. 17 (Box 69, Folder 89)
    - L.J. Ayres, Amherst County Sheriff photo op, 2004 Apr. 13 (Box 69, Folder 90)
    - Executive Order signing with Delegate Reese, 2004 Apr. 20 (Box 69, Folder 91)
    - Great Virginia Teach-in signing, 2004 Apr. 21 (Box 69, Folder 92)
    - Bill signings, HB 1313 and HB 1096, 2004 Apr. 21 (Box 69, Folder 92)
    - Brown v. Board of Education conference, 2004 Apr. 21 (Box 69, Folder 92)
    - Easter Seals Virginia photo op, 2004 Apr. 21 (Box 69, Folder 92)
    - Ms. Wheelchair Virginia photo op, 2004 Apr. 21 (Box 69, Folder 92)
    - Virginia Association of Volunteer Rescue photo op, 2004 Apr. 21 (Box 69, Folder 92)
    - Economic development announcement, 2004 Apr. 23 (Box 69, Folder 93)
    - PASS school visits, 2004 Apr. 23 (Box 69, Folder 93)
    - Bill signings, HB 1207, HB 1208, SB 436, HB 415, and HB 949, 2004 Apr. 27 (Box 69, Folder 94)
    - Cabinet photos, 2004 May 3 (Box 69, Folder 95)
    - Project Graduation, 2004 May 3 (Box 69, Folder 96)
    - Law enforcement summit, 2004 May 5 (Box 69, Folder 97)
    - Constituent Services interns photo op, 2004 May 6 (Box 69, Folder 98)
    - Bill signing with VCU social work students and faculty, 2004 May 6 (Box 69, Folder 98)
    - Bill signing, HB 805, 2004 May 6 (Box 69, Folder 98)
    - FAMIS and Cover the Uninsured Week press event, 2004 May 10 (Box 69, Folder 99)
    - Spring agency head meeting, 2004 May 10 (Box 69, Folder 100)
    - Tech. award, 2004 May 10 (Box 69, Folder 101)
    - Race to GED kick-off, 2004 May 13 (Box 69, Folder 102)
    - National WWII Memorial check presentation, 2004 May 13 (Box 69, Folder 102)
    - Reporting Back event, VCU School of Education, 2004 May 14 (Box 69, Folder 103)
    - Governor's Business Appreciation breakfast, 2004 May 17 (Box 69, Folder 104)
    - Blackwell Elementary PASS celebration, 2004 May 17 (Box 69, Folder 105)
    - Unveling of Virginia's Heritage Music Trail signage, 2004 May 19 (Box 69, Folder 106)
    - Reporting Back event, 2004 May 19 (Box 69, Folder 106)
    - Ribbon cutting at Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind energy system, 2004 May 24 (Box 69, Folder 107)
    - Reporting Back events, 2004 May 24 (Box 69, Folder 107)
    - Press conference on gangs, 2004 May 24 (Box 69, Folder 107)
    - Leadership Emporia-Greensville Capitol visit, 2004 May 26 (Box 69, Folder 108)
    - VDACS meeting, 2004 May 26 (Box 69, Folder 109)
    - Senor Jorge Conde photo op, 2004 May 26 (Box 69, Folder 109)
    - AOL/Governor's Technology Awards, 2004 May 27 (Box 69, Folder 110)
    - D.U.I. bill signings, 2004 May 27 (Box 69, Folder 111)
    - Russ Parr Morning Show radio broadcast, 2004 May 28 (Box 69, Folder 112)
    - DHCD Homeownership Month Habitat for Humanity event, 2004 June 1 (Box 69, Folder 113)
    - Bill signings, HB 5018, HB 1177, SB 533, HB 891, SB 652, HB 952, SB 318, HB 334, and HB 1015, 2004 June 16 (Box 69, Folder 114)
    - Southside Broadband Initiative announcement, 2004 June 18 (Box 69, Folder 115)
    - Governor's Fellows reception, 2004 June 22 (Box 69, Folder 116)
    - Bill signings, HB 717, SB 333, SB 648, HB 1398, HB 1261, and HB 20, 2004 June 23 (Box 69, Folder 117)
    - Boys State, 2004 June 24 (Box 69, Folder 118)
    - Girls State, 2004 June 24 (Box 69, Folder 118)
    - NARFE Executive Committee, 2004 July 13 (Box 69, Folder 119)
    - National Governors Association conference, Seattle, WA, 2004 July 18 (Box 69, Folder 120)
    - Jamestown 2007 announcement, 2004 July 21 (Box 69, Folder 121)
    - Bill signings, 2004 July 21 (Box 69, Folder 122)
    - Question and answer session with Governor's Fellows, 2004 July 21 (Box 69, Folder 122)
    - 21st Annual National Night Out, 2004 Aug. 3 (Box 69, Folder 123)
    - Lite 98 and VDACS Farmers' Market event, 2004 Aug. 5 (Box 69, Folder 124)
    - Fiddler's Convention, youth competition, 2004 Aug. 9 (Box 69, Folder 125)
    - Governor's bike ride, New River Trail, 2004 Aug. 9 (Box 69, Folder 125)
    - Lunch at Big Daddy's Restaurant, Fries, VA, 2004 Aug. 9 (Box 69, Folder 125)
    - BRAC visit to Langley, 2004 Aug. 18 (Box 69, Folder 126)
    - BRAC visit to Quantico, 2004 Aug. 24 (Box 69, Folder 127)
    - Rafting on the James River with the Kaine family, 2004 Aug. 27 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Giles County Public Schools convocation, 2004 Sept. 2 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Celanese Acetate visit, 2004 Sept. 2 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Lunch at Motor Mile Speedway with Keister, 2004 Sept. 2 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Art Museum of Western Virginia, 2004 Sept. 2 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Onzlee Ware event, 2004 Sept. 2 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Happy Hour with a Purpose, 2004 Sept. 2 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Ribbon cutting for Kent Square, 2004 Sept. 3 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Tech Corps of Cadets visit, 2004 Sept. 3 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Hospital Association reception, 2004 Sept. 15 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Healthy Virginia event, 2004 Nov. 18 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Agency heads mansion reception, 2004 Dec. 20 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Holiday reception with Capitol Police, 2004 Dec. 21 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, 2004 (1 of 2) (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, 2004 (2 of 2) (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Association of Elementary School Principals visit, 2005 Jan. 31 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Legislative aides' reception, 2005 Jan. 31 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - House legislators' reception, 2005 Feb. 2 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Mine safety legislation, 2005 Feb. 10 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Exceptional Children's Week, 2005 Feb. 10 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Photo op with Sallie Mae, 2005 Feb. 11 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Pages' reception, 2005 Feb. 14 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - SCHEV Outstanding Faculty Awards, 2005 Feb. 15 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Tech visit with Bill Leighty, 2005 Feb. 15 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - UAW/GM Powertrain, 2005 Feb. 17 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Wilderness Institute photo op, 2005 Feb. 23 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Assistant City Manager of Danville photo op, 2005 Feb. 23 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Norfolk Saints football team photo op, 2005 Feb. 23 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Engineering Week, 2005 Feb. 25 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Read Across America Day, 2005 Mar. 4 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Virginia First Robotics Competition, 2005 Mar. 4 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Congressional Delegation meeting, 2005 Mar. 14 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Governor Warner and Margaret Spellings, Huguenot High School, 2005 Mar. 16 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - National Geographic/Appalachia announcement, 2005 Mar. 21 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Food tax reduction bill signing, 2005 Mar. 22 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Assisted living facilities bill signing, 2005 Mar. 23 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - DJJ employee recognition event, 2005 Mar. 23 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Bill signings, HB 1847, HB 2412, HB 2425, HB 2266, SB 843, SB 1006, HB 2245, and HB 2762, 2005 Apr. 5 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Photo op with Jay Matthews, 2005 Apr. 5 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - New Jersey legislative staff visit, 2005 Apr. 6 (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Motorsports Day, 2005 Apr. 6 (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Bill signings, SB 1174 and HB 2739, 2005 Apr. 13 (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Norfolk City Charter bill signing, 2005 Apr. 13 (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Bill signing, SB 1202, 2005 Apr. 15 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Chambliss Elementary School visit, 2005 May 3 (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Jackson Elementary School visit, 2005 May 3 (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Mansion reception for veterans, 2005 June 8 (Box 70, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 31)
    - Cabinet photographs, undated (Box 70, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (1 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (2 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (3 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (4 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (5 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (6 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (7 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (8 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (9 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 41)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (10 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (11 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (12 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (13 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (14 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 46)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (15 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 47)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (16 of 16) (Box 70, Folder 48)
    - Oversize Cabinet photographs, undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Oversize Arlington Police Department photograph, undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Series IV. Press material, 2001-2006 (Accession 42626).
  Notes and speech-writing material including reports, memos, correspondence and other working papers collected by Governor Warner's Press Office staff. They may be the files of Deputy Press Secretary Kevin Hall, but this is unclear. This small series contains several folders of notepads containing names and contact information, as well as what appear to be meeting notes spanning most of the Governor's term in office. Also included in this series is reference material collected and used for drafting speeches and statements, and for keeping abreast of current issues. Some folders cover broad topics, others contain a particular report, such as the Governor's Proposed Amendments for 2004-2006 Appropriation Act (HB 5001), or information pertaining to a specific program, such as the Partnership for Achieving Successful Schools (PASS) program. Additionally, there are also several folders of notes, revisions, and final drafts of selected speeches and statements issued by the Governor. Notable issues include the Base Realignment and Closure process that threatened Oceana Naval Base in Virginia Beach, the voter redistricting controversy, and the Virginia Tech Board of Visitors decision regarding discrimination. There are also several folders devoted to budgetary and tax issues that contain reports and other documentation created by the Department of Planning and Budget that may not be found elsewhere. For more information on speeches and statements made by Governor Warner, please see Series VII. Speeches.
  - Notes, 2002-2005 (1 of 7) (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Notes, 2002-2005 (2 of 7) (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Notes, 2002-2005 (3 of 7) (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Notes, 2002-2005 (4 of 7) (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Notes, 2002-2005 (5 of 7) (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Notes, 2002-2005 (6 of 7) (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Notes, 2002-2005 (7 of 7) (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Reference material--Actual General Fund Revenues for FY2005 and the State of the Virginia Economy presentation, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Reference material--Aircraft Accident/Incident Action Plan, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Reference material--Baseball in Northern Virginia, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Reference material--Base Realignment and Closure (BRAC), 2005 (1 of 3) (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Reference material--Base Realignment and Closure (BRAC), 2005 (2 of 3) (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Reference material--Base Realignment and Closure (BRAC), 2005 (3 of 3) (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Reference material--Budget and tax, 2002-2005 (1 of 4) (Box 72, Folder 14)